You could call Oren Little 'charming' — except no one does.
And So It Goes is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Rob Reiner.
Nobody likes self-centered realtor Oren Little, and he prefers it that way.
He's deliberately mean to anyone who crosses his path and wants
nothing more than to sell one final house and retire.
His life turns upside-down when his estranged son drops
off a granddaughter he never knew existed.
Suddenly left in charge of her and with no idea how to take care of a child, he pawns the girl
off on his neighbor, Leah -- but he eventually learns how to open his heart.
Oren Little, played by Michael Douglas.
Leah, played by Diane Keaton.
Sarah, played by Sterling Jerins.
Selena, played by Paloma Guzmán.
Claire, played by Frances Sternhagen.
Club Owner, played by Frankie Valli.
And So It Goes is a 2014 American comedy drama film directed
by Rob Reiner and written by Mark Andrus.
The film, which stars Michael Douglas, Diane Keaton and
Sterling Jerins, was released on July 25, 2014.
It received mostly negative reviews from critics, and
performed modestly at the box office.
The film was the second collaboration between Reiner and
Douglas, after The American President (1995).
This film was also Frances Sternhagen's final feature film
role before her death on November 27, 2023.
The film explores themes of grandparent grandchild relationship,
neighbor, wealthy, falling in love, real estate agent.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.